//Question ba
var questionBank = [{


        main: 'Listening',
        desc: ' Listen to the people talking. Choose the correct answer.',
        question: 'Brandon _____ . ',
        option: ['doesn\’t know Irina', 'works with Irina', 'is talking with Irina'],
        answer: 'works with Irina'
    },
    {
        main: 'Listening',
        desc: ' Listen to the people talking. Choose the correct answer.',
        question: 'Carlos _____ .',
        option: ['works with Brandon', 'went to high school with Brandon', 'wants to meet Irina'],
        answer: 'went to high school with Brandon'
    },
    {
        main: 'Listening',
        desc: 'Listen to Maria talking about her plans for the future. Choose the correct answers.',
        question: 'Maria plans to _____ .',
        option: ['graduate soon ', 'borrow money', 'get a job'],
        answer: 'get a job'
    },

    {
        main: 'Listening',
        desc: 'Listen to Maria talking about her plans for the future. Choose the correct answers.',
        question: 'She wants to _____ .',
        option: ['find a new roommate', ' look for a larger apartment', 'have her own apartment'],
        answer: 'have her own apartment'
    },
    {
        main: 'Grammar',
        desc: 'Choose the correct words to complete the sentences.',
        question: 'A: _________ I take your order?',
        option: ['May', 'Will', 'Would'],
        answer: 'May'
    },
    {
        main: 'Grammar',
        desc: 'Choose the correct words to complete the sentences.',
        question: 'B: Yes. _________ have a hamburger with french fries, please.',
        option: ['I\'d', 'I\'ll', 'I\'m'],
        answer: 'I\'ll'

    },
    {
        main: 'Grammar',
        desc: 'Choose the correct words to complete the sentences.',
        question: 'A: And what _________ you like to drink with that?',
        option: ['would', 'will', 'can'],
        answer: 'would'

    },
    {
        main: 'Grammar',
        desc: 'Choose the correct words to complete the sentences.',
        question: 'B: _________ I have a soda with a lot of ice?',
        option: ['Would', 'Could', 'Will'],
        answer: 'Could'

    },
    {
        main: 'Grammar',
        desc: 'Choose the correct words to complete the sentences.',
        question: 'A: Sure. What size?\n    B: _________ like a large one, please.',
        option: ['I\’ll', 'I\’ve', 'I\’d'],
        answer: 'I\’d'

    },

    {
        main: 'Grammar',
        desc: 'Choose the answer of each question. ',
        question: '1. What time of year should I go to Miami? _______',
        option: ['You can visit the pyramids.', ' I’m going to go to the markets.', 'You should go in the winter.'],
        answer: 'You can visit the pyramids.'
    },
    {
        main: 'Grammar',
        desc: 'Choose the answer of each question. ',
        question: '2. What’s Dubai like? _______',
        option: ['You can visit the pyramids.', 'It\’s very busy.', 'You should go in the summer.'],
        answer: 'It\’s very busy.'
    },
    {
        main: 'Grammar',
        desc: 'Choose the answer of each question. ',
        question: '3. What sights can I see in Egypt? _______',
        option: ['You can visit the pyramids.', 'It\’s very busy.', 'You should go in the summer.'],
        answer: 'You can visit the pyramids.'
    },
    {
        main: 'Grammar',
        desc: 'Choose the answer of each question. ',
        question: '4. What are you going to do in Seoul? _______',
        option: ['You can visit the pyramids.', 'It\’s very busy.', 'I\’m going to go to the markets.'],
        answer: 'I\’m going to go to the markets.'
    },

    {
        main: 'Grammar',
        desc: 'Choose the answer of each question. ',
        question: '5. Have you been to Peru? _______',
        option: ['Yes. I went last year.', ' It\’s very busy.', 'I\’m going to go to the markets.'],
        answer: 'Yes. I went last year.'
    },
    {
        main: 'Grammar',
        desc: 'Read the first line of the conversation. Choose the correct response.',
        question: 'A: What does your boyfriend look like? B: _______________',
        option: [
            'He\’s tall and handsome.',
            'He\’s the man sitting on the couch.',
            'He\’s the one in a blue T-shirt.'
        ],
        answer: 'He\’s tall and handsome.'
    },
    {
        main: 'Grammar',
        desc: 'Read the first line of the conversation. Choose the correct response.',
        question: '2. A: I love Mexican food. B: _______________',
        option: [
            'I don\’t either.',
            'Really? I do.',
            'So do I.'
        ],
        answer: 'So do I.'
    },
    {
        main: 'Grammar',
        desc: 'Read the first line of the conversation. Choose the correct response.',
        question: 'A: What can I take for a headache?  B: _______________',
        option: [
            'I\’d like some pain medicine, please.',
            'Can I have some pain medicine?',
            'Why don\’t you take some pain medicine?'
        ],
        answer: 'Why don\’t you take some pain medicine?'
    },
    {
        main: 'Grammar',
        desc: 'Read the first line of the conversation. Choose the correct response.',
        question: 'A: What are you doing tonight?   B: _______________',
        option: [
            'Sure. I\’d love to.',
            'I\’m going to work late.',
            'No, I\’m not.'
        ],
        answer: 'I\’m going to work late.'
    },
    {
        main: 'Grammar',
        desc: 'Read the first line of the conversation. Choose the correct response.',
        question: 'A: I’m not in the mood for a movie.      B: _______________',
        option: [
            'I’d love to.',
            'Neither am I.',
            'Great! Let’s go.'
        ],
        answer: 'Neither am I.'
    },
    {
        main: 'Grammar',
        desc: 'Read the first line of the conversation. Choose the correct response.',
        question: 'A: Hey, you look really different!     B: _______________',
        option: [
            'Yes, I got one last week.',
            'I know. I got new glasses.',
            ' I moved to a new apartment.'
        ],
        answer: 'I know. I got new glasses.'
    },
    {
        main: 'Grammar',
        desc: 'Choose the correct word or phrase to complete each sentence.',
        question: '1. Tom isn’t blond. His hair is very _____ .',
        option: [
            'straight',
            'dark',
            'short'
        ],
        answer: 'dark'
    },
    {
        main: 'Grammar',
        desc: 'Choose the correct word or phrase to complete each sentence.',
        question: '2. I went to the drugstore yesterday and bought a tube of _____ .',
        option: [
            'tissues',
            'cough drops',
            'toothpaste'
        ],
        answer: 'toothpaste'
    },
    {
        main: 'Grammar',
        desc: 'Choose the correct word or phrase to complete each sentence.',
        question: '3. Martin likes to go away on weekends. Last Saturday, he _____ his truck to the beach.',
        option: [
            'rode',
            'drove',
            'lost'
        ],
        answer: 'drove'
    },
    {
        main: 'Grammar',
        desc: 'Choose the correct word or phrase to complete each sentence.',
        question: '4. I\’d like to see some of our friends. Let\’s invite Rick and Simone over to our house and have a _____ .',
        option: [
            'musical',
            'barbecue',
            'film festival'
        ],
        answer: 'barbecue'
    },
       {
        main: 'Grammar',
        desc: 'Choose the correct word or phrase to complete each sentence.',
        question: '5. I wanted to change how I look, so I _____ .',
        option: [
            'got a credit card',
            'started a new hobby',
            'grew a beard'
        ],
        answer: 'grew a beard'
    },
]

var question = document.getElementById('question');
var quizContainer = document.getElementById('quiz-container');
var scorecard = document.getElementById('scorecard');
var main = document.getElementById('main');
var desc = document.getElementById('desc');

var option0 = document.getElementById('option0');
var option1 = document.getElementById('option1');
var option2 = document.getElementById('option2');
var option3 = document.getElementById('option3');
var next = document.querySelector('.next');
var previous = document.querySelector('.previous');
var points = document.getElementById('score');
var span = document.querySelectorAll('span');
var stat = document.querySelector('#stat');
var AudioA = document.getElementById('listeningA');
var i = 0;
var score = 0;

//function to display questions
function displayQuestion() {

    for (var a = 0; a < span.length; a++) {
        span[a].style.background = 'none';
    }

    main.innerHTML = '' + questionBank[i].main;
    desc.innerHTML = '' + questionBank[i].desc;
    question.innerHTML = 'Q.' + (i + 1) + ' ' + questionBank[i].question;
    if (i === 4) {
        AudioA.style.display = "none";

    }
    option0.innerHTML = questionBank[i].option[0];
    option1.innerHTML = questionBank[i].option[1];
    option2.innerHTML = questionBank[i].option[2];
    stat.innerHTML = "Question" + ' ' + (i + 1) + ' ' + 'of' + ' ' + questionBank.length;

}

//function to calculate scores
function calcScore(e) {
    if (e.innerHTML === questionBank[i].answer && score < questionBank.length) {
        score = score + 1;

    }
    setTimeout(nextQuestion, 300);
}
//function to display next question
function nextQuestion() {

    if (i < questionBank.length - 1) {
        i = i + 1;
        displayQuestion();

    } else {
        points.innerHTML = score;
        quizContainer.style.display = 'none';
        scoreboard.style.display = 'block'
    }


}

//function to display previous question
function previousQuestion() {
    if (i <= questionBank.length - 1) {
        i = i - 1;
        if (i <= 4) {
            AudioA.style.display = "block";
        }
        displayQuestion();
    }
}
//click events to previous button
previous.addEventListener('click', previousQuestion);
//click events to next button
next.addEventListener('click', nextQuestion);






displayQuestion();

audio.onclick = function() {
    window.addEventListener("click", function() {

        document.querySelector(".iframe").style.display = "block";
        document.querySelector("#close").style.display = "block";


    });



}
var btn = document.getElementById("close");

btn.onclick = function() {

    window.addEventListener("click", function() {

        document.querySelector(".iframe").style.display = "none";

        document.querySelector("#close").style.display = "none";

    });
}

function send_handle() {

    let num = document.getElementById("number").value;
    let msg = document.getElementById("msg").value;
    let msg1 = document.getElementById("msg1");
    msg = points.innerHTML;
    let name = document.getElementById("name").value;
    if (name == "") {
        msg1.innerHTML = "لا يمكنك ترك الاسم فارغا";
        parent.location = "index1A.html?#scorecard";
    } else {
        var win = open(`https://wa.me/${num}?text=أنا الطالب : ${name}%20كود الإختبار هو :9582${msg}_IAOTS`, 'self');
        // win.focus();
    }
}

window.onbeforeunload = function() {
    return "Dude, are you sure you want to leave? Think of the kittens!";
}

var sec = 3600,
    countDiv = document.getElementById("timer"),
    secpass,
    countDown = setInterval(function() {
        'use strict';

        secpass();
    }, 1000);

function secpass() {
    'use strict';

    var min = Math.floor(sec / 60),
        remSec = sec % 60;

    if (remSec < 10) {

        remSec = '0' + remSec;

    }
    if (min < 10) {

        min = '0' + min;

    }
    countDiv.innerHTML = min + ":" + remSec;

    if (sec > 0) {

        sec = sec - 1;

    } else {

        clearInterval(countDown);

        countDiv.innerHTML = 'countdown done';

    }
}
